ANTON SHTIPLIYSKI

WEB DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE

Front-End Web Developer | Salefish Online

NOV 2020 - PRESENT

- Implementing front end features. Currently working with Vue.js / Vuex, C# and SQL database. Creating reusable code and components on applications in production. Deploying new features to our test and live production web sites.
- Assist with UX/UI design, making sure all features and pages are responsive (built mobile first).
- Collaborating in a team with backend developers and marketing team.

Freelance Web Developer | Akeeva.co

OCT 2020 - NOV 2020

 Worked on a Full-Stack Web Development project using MERN stack, Next.js and Redux.

Reservation Sales Agent | Accor

JUL 2019 - NOV 2020, MONCTON, NB

- Handled high volume of calls on a daily basis, while making sure that the best value was presented. Worked simultaneously with few different programs.
- Built strong professional relationships with collages and management.
 Trained for management position. Problem solving on a daily basis.

Casino Supervisor | Carnival and Celebrity Cruise Lines

MAY 2012 - MAY 2018, MIAMI, FL

- Solving problems has been huge part of my daily routine. Managed up to 50 workers in Casino environment and up to 950 guests while on safety drills. Completed training for Assistant Manager.
- Handled yearly, quarterly, monthly and weekly reports.
- Responsible for creating work schedules for staff and management.
 Evaluated employees prepared and presented appraisals. Trained staff to become supervisors and learn new games.

EDUCATION

BrainStation | Diploma Candidate, Web Development

MAY 2020 - AUG 2020, TORONTO, ON

Vocational High School | Vocational Certificate / High School Diploma, Technology of Environmental Protection

SEP 2004 - 2009, Bulgaria, Sofia

antonshtipliyski@yahoo.com 437-245-7861 linkedin.com/in/anton-shtipliyski github.com/ahshtipliyski

SKILLS:

HTML5, CSS3, Sass, Javascript (ES6), React.js, Next.js, Vue.js, Bootstrap, Node.js, Express.js, API Implementation, C# .NET, SQL, Postman, Jira, Git, Firebase, Heroku

PROFILE:

I believe that technology is breaking down barriers for us to better perform mentally, physically, and socially. From my previous experience I have proven myself to be very efficient and quick learner, even while working under pressure. Since I started my journey as a web developer, I have been learning new technologies on a daily basis and I am excited continue learning and keep improving.

PROJECTS:

https://ahshtipliyski.github.io